(All people, incidents,
and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious
and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children were filmed
under production guidelines.)
(Episode 13)
What brings you here?
I'm here for my portfolio.
Oh, dear. Don't you know
submissions aren't returned?
I'd still like it back.
It's just trash to you anyway.
True. Wait a second.
Shouldn't you say thank you
before taking it?
I know it was you
who ruined my score.
Says who?
Am I wrong?
That's right.
I made sure you failed.
I told you.
As long as I'm around,
you'll never get a job here.
We'll see about that.
What?
You think the likes of you
can stop me?
What? The likes of me?
You little...
Look at you. Some habits die hard.
Let go of me!
Hey.
Listen up.
If I were going to quit now,
I wouldn't have even started.
So what else can you do?
You'll just have to wait and see.
So just you wait.
I'll show you exactly what I can do.
I get it.
Of course you're feeling desperate.
I understand.
You tried so hard,
only to fail because of me.
Of course you'd be upset.
Go ahead and do whatever you want.
At this point, I'm actually curious
to see what you'll do.
What are you still doing here?
Just get lost already.
Fine. See you around.
So proud, right to the end.
What are you going to do now?
I have to expose
what Kang Hae Ra did.
Expose her? To whom?
To the CEO.
You know that Ms. Kang is
the CEO's daughter, right?
Yes.
Blood is thicker than water.
Do you think telling the CEO
will have any effect?
I've got to give it a shot.
That being said, can you find out
the CEO's schedule for me?
Sure.
He has a meeting
with business leaders at 6 p.m.,
so he'll be leaving the office
around five.
- CEO Kang.
- What's this about?
I have something to say to the CEO.
Sir, this competition wasn't fair.
Kang Hae Ra disqualified me
out of a personal grudge.
You know my Hae Ra?
Yes, we went
to high school together.
What's your name?
It's Ko Eun Seol.
So you're saying my Hae Ra
deliberately disqualified you?
Yes.
I'd like you to review
my portfolio again.
If that's what this is about,
talk to the staff in charge.
- Let's go.
- Yes, sir. Move aside.
What are you looking at
so seriously?
Unbelievable.
When will Hae Ra be home?
She should be here soon.
It's the judge's score sheet
for the competition.
What is it? Is there a problem?
I'm home.
Hae Ra, come here.
Why?
Is contestant number 97 Ko Eun Seol?
How do you know that, Dad?
And she was your classmate?
Don't tell me she came to see you.
She did.
She said you disqualified her
for personal reasons.
Unbelievable.
Can you do anything right?
Dad, I was just making sure
the guidelines were followed.
She's the one who broke them.
Then why did all the other judges
give her high scores?
Well, that's...
If you wanted to fail her,
you shouldn't have made it
so obvious.
What will you do if she goes
to the press and says...
the CEO's daughter
is power-tripping?
Surely she wouldn't go that far.
That's because you haven't met her.
She's no pushover.
Then just reverse the decision now.
You said all the other judges
gave her high scores.
Absolutely not, Mom.
Yes, Hae Ra is right about that.
If we reverse the decision now,
it'd be like admitting the company
made a mistake.
Then what? What if she goes around
telling everyone, like you said?
I don't think she'll do that.
How can you be so sure,
Director Joo?
If anything like that happens,
I'll handle it myself.
Please don't worry too much, sir.
Anyway, Hae Ra,
keep disappointing me
and see what happens.
Ko Eun Seol...
So the best you could do
was tattle to my dad?
Hae Ra.
Did you really disqualify
your friend on purpose?
A friend, as if.
She's my worst enemy.
She's so immature.
What am I going to do with her?
How did it go?
Were you able to meet with the CEO?
Yes.
But you were right, Attorney Seo.
He wouldn't even give me
the time of day.
I figured as much.
That must've really upset you.
Well, I was somewhat prepared
for it, so I'm fine.
You don't have to act tough with me.
Anyway,
now that even the CEO
has turned you down,
what's your next move?
If the CEO won't help,
I'll have to go see Chairman Kim.
Do you really think
she won't favor her own side?
I have to hope
that she'll be different.
I'd like you to review
my portfolio again.
If that's what this is about,
talk to the staff in charge.
- Let's go.
- Yes, sir. Move aside.
Mr. Seok Jin.
- Mr. Seok Jin.
- Yes?
What is it, Mom?
I asked
what you thought of my drawing.
Right.
No way. It's really good.
You're getting better and better.
But...
Mr. Seok Jin, you seem upset.
Oh, right.
It's not what you think.
There's just someone
I can't stop thinking about.
Who is it?
Just someone. Someone who hurt me.
How mean of them.
Should I teach them a lesson?
Anyway, this stands for love.
That Ko Eun Seol girl might
come to see you as well,
so I'll escort you myself
for a while.
Is that really necessary?
If she shows up,
I can just calm her down.
Absolutely not.
If you give her an inch,
she'll take a mile.
You have to nip it in the bud.
All right.
What's this?
- You're as beautiful as ever,
- My gosh.
actress Kim Jung Sun.
What is it, ma'am?
I think it's him.
The stalker.
Didn't you say he was in prison?
He must've been released.
Then what do I do?
Don't worry.
I'll assign you a security detail.
(Cheongchun Gositel)
It was originally mine.
I'm just taking it back.
I...
I have to get into Cheongma,
no matter what.
What's this?
- Did he leave this here?
- Get rid of it now.
Madam Chairman. Ma'am!
- You can't do this here.
- Please.
It'll only take a moment.
- Leave.
- Ma'am!
- Please. Just let me talk to her.
- You can't.
Ma'am, just a moment. Ma'am!
Ma'am, please hear me out.
Madam Chairman!
Here, have some of this.
Thanks.
(Cheongma Scholarship Foundation,
Chairman Kim Jung Sun)
Are you feeling better now?
Yes.
Mom. I heard your stalker showed up.
- He did.
- He left flowers at the house.
That's insane.
So, are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
What should we do about
next week's 50th anniversary event?
Perhaps we should cancel
your appearance on the runway.
Of course.
I'll take your place,
so don't worry, Mom.
No. If I cancel, that means he wins,
and I can't let that happen.
But still...
Won't it be too dangerous?
Director Joo will be there,
and so will the bodyguards.
What's there to worry about?
By the way,
that young woman from earlier...
She must be Hae Ra's old classmate.
I guess so.
Wait, did Ko Eun Seol
come to see you too?
She's even crazier than I thought.
She's the young woman from before.
From before?
Who are you talking about?
The girl who saved her dad
as "My Dearest Dad" in her contacts.
No way.
Are you saying you compared me
to a girl like that?
Hae Ra, why do you hate her so much?
She seemed nice enough.
What's so nice about her?
Mom, are you seriously praising her
in front of me?
Team Leader Kang!
The Chairman is in shock
and having a hard time.
What are you doing? That's enough.
Fine.
Ma'am, you shouldn't worry
about a girl like that anymore.
I guess...
I have my own problems.
Here, have some water.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to see Chairman Kim.
Have you been waiting here
like this all day?
Yes.
Let's go talk somewhere.
We can talk here.
Follow me.
Do you really have to go this far?
- What do you mean?
- You're doing this...
because you think you got wronged.
- That's right.
- Exactly.
So, is this really necessary?
Like you said,
I was unfairly eliminated.
This won't change anything.
You'll only end up
looking more pathetic.
So just stop here.
Is that what you wanted
to talk to me about?
Ko Eun Seol...
Since you're involved,
you must know...
that Kang Hae Ra gave me a zero.
She was just exercising
her authority as a judge.
It was an abuse of power
under the guise of authority.
Why are you going to such lengths?
Are you this desperate
to get into Cheongma?
Yes.
What?
If we're done here,
I'll be on my way.
Please, have a seat.
Ms. Joo,
what brings you to my office?
Chairman Kim's stalker
was released from prison.
The man who was arrested
two years ago?
Yes.
Has he made contact again since?
Here.
(You're as beautiful as ever,
actress Kim Jung Sun.)
Is this enough to get
a restraining order?
It's certainly worth a try.
Will it be possible
before next week's 50th anniversary event?
I can't guarantee that.
There's a procedure
we have to follow.
Then,
it seems we have no choice
but to increase security.
Right.
Yes, this is it.
You can stop here, please.
Okay, get as close as you can.
Yes, that's good.
Eun Guk, come on, let's go.
Welcome.
Right, hello.
Thanks again
for letting us rent the annex.
Well, it's not like
I'm letting you stay for free.
I know, but still.
But you should really do something
about your son's clothes.
Come on, it's embarrassing.
What's wrong with my clothes?
Should I wear long sleeves
when it's boiling hot?
My gosh, that's gross.
So many people would kill
for this body.
She doesn't get it.
You shameless punk.
- Okay, I think we're almost done.
- Right.
Should we order jjajangmyeon?
Oh, good idea.
But first, go get your grandma.
Oh, right. Grandma.
Got it. I'll go get her now.
- Okay. And be nice about it.
- Sure.
If she won't budge,
try tempting her with jjajangmyeon.
Don't tell me
they actually ditched me.
Grandma.
Grandma,
we're done with the move,
so let's go.
How many times do I have to tell you
I'm not going?
Don't be like that. Let's go.
Then, don't let Eun Seol
into the house.
I can't do that, Grandma.
Eun Guk, you...
If you hate Eun Seol that much,
then you should go ask
your favorite fortune-teller.
Ask them
whether Eun Seol really did it.
I already did.
You think I wouldn't have?
And?
What did they say?
They said Eun Seol
didn't do it, right?
But you can't believe everything
a fortune-teller says.
At this point,
it's not that you can't believe it.
It's that you don't want
to believe it.
You're actually hoping that
Eun Seol really did it.
What? What kind of person
do you take me for?
No matter
how much I may hate Eun Seol,
how could you say
something like that?
Then if you don't want me
to think that,
get up right now.
Because if you don't,
I'm just going to keep
thinking that.
But...
See?
It feels unfair to be misunderstood,
doesn't it?
Imagine how Eun Seol must feel.
Grandma, you're hungry, aren't you?
Gosh, I'm starving too.
So let's go quickly...
and order jjajangmyeon,
your favorite. Okay?
- Come on.
- Just stop it.
My bag. Okay, I'll get up.
Let's go.
Oh, hey. Welcome home.
I'm sorry I couldn't help
with the move, Dad.
It wasn't much of a move.
We pretty much
threw everything away.
You're here.
It's been a while, Eun Guk.
Grandma, Eun Seol's here.
So what if she's here?
What do you want me to do?
Mom, come on.
Go on in and get some rest.
You must be tired.
- Okay.
- Right.
- Unbelievable.
You should go rest too, Mom.
You must be tired.
You go rest.
Why go through all the hassle
of getting a restraining order?
Just have him thrown in jail,
or hire someone to scare him off.
Do you think
this is a lawless country?
We can't just throw people in jail.
He's not just anyone.
He's a stalker.
Besides, there are laws.
Should the owner's family
act above them?
Are you trying to ruin the company?
Honestly,
how does it make sense
that the Chairman of Cheongma...
is being threatened by a stalker?
We have money and connections.
It's ridiculous
we can't handle one stalker.
The CEO is right.
If things go wrong, the perpetrator
could be seen as the victim.
That would be a huge risk
for the company.
It's best to do things legally.
I've seen plenty of people
get burned for trusting the law.
What's the point of having
all this money and power?
This is so frustrating.
- Unbelievable.
- My gosh.
You don't need to worry
about him either.
We have bodyguards.
You don't know
unless you've lived it.
The pain is so real.
What are you doing out here?
Attorney Seo.
I couldn't sleep.
By the way,
is there really no way
I can meet Chairman Kim?
Well, there's next week's
50th anniversary event.
The 50th anniversary event?
Chairman Kim is scheduled
to walk the runway that day.
So I could create an opportunity?
Please, get me in.
I'll handle the rest from there.
All right.
I'll get you an invitation,
and you can give it a shot.
But you have to be
extremely careful.
Okay?
Got it.
(Lowering Barriers,
Filling Lives With Warmth)
(Cheongma Group
50th Anniversary Event)
Yes, Attorney Seo.
Chairman Kim is
in the basement waiting room.
Okay, got it.
How did you get in here?
I was invited.
Who invited you?
Show me your invitation.
Satisfied?
Where are you going?
I'm just going to the restroom.
- Madam Chairman!
- Be quiet.
Or this woman dies.
All right.
Okay, I get it. Just calm down.
What do you want from me?
Why are you doing this?
You still don't know?
There's only one thing I want.
Your love.
Please, don't do this.
Let's talk this out.
No.
I'm exhausted now.
If I can't have you,
we might as well die together.
Today's that day.
Please... Please don't do this.
This isn't love.
Ma'am, run!
Help!
- Help.
- Are you all right?
In there...
No, my love.
Ma'am!
Ma'am, are you all right?
I'm fine. Go check inside. Hurry.
Oh no.
Eun Seol, are you okay?
Blood...
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
You're bleeding.
- Oh no.
- What happened?
- Easy now.
- Okay.
Thank you.
I can't believe this.
Do you not have any fear at all?
What were you thinking,
taking on someone with a knife?
It was a desperate situation.
It doesn't matter
how desperate it was.
Do you have a death wish?
Why are you mad at me?
I wasn't the one
waving a knife around.
I'm sorry to ask,
but could you see
if I can switch rooms?
This is a little much.
Don't worry about it.
Anyway, how's Chairman Kim?
Ma'am, are you okay?
Where am I?
Don't worry. You're home.
I'm sorry.
I should've paid closer attention.
Who would've thought he'd be hiding
in the women's restroom?
But what about that young woman?
Was she badly hurt?
No, she just needed a few stitches.
You don't need to worry.
If it hadn't been for her,
something awful could've happened.
Try not to think about it
and get some more sleep.
The sedative is kicking in now,
so you'll calm down soon.
Get some sleep, okay?
Why did it have to be Ko Eun Seol?
How's my wife?
She was just given a sedative.
She should be fine now.
How did the anniversary event go?
Given the scene this morning,
do you think it turned out okay?
Why weren't you there
escorting her, Director Joo?
I'm very sorry, sir.
(A Trap Called Desire)
- Kang Hae Ra.
- You don't care how I feel, do you?
Do you have any idea
how I felt earlier?
My blood ran cold.
I'm the one
who's disappointed in you.
Do you two know each other?
Now that Attorney Seo is here,
you can go, Seok Jin.
No way, Mom.
A stranger would think Ko Eun Seol
is your daughter, not me.
How can I be another burden to you?
No matter how I think about it,
it's just not right.
I'd like to offer you
financial compensation.
I'd like a job at Cheongma.
That's out of the question, Ms. Ko.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)